<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ws>
    <settings>
        <stage width="900px" height="460px" create="yes" center="yes" />
    </settings>
    <assets>
        
        <imagepack name="tourist" x="410px" y="150px" z="20">
            <image src="assets/images/tourist_angry.png" name="angry" />
            <image src="assets/images/tourist_calm.png" name="calm" />
            <image src="assets/images/tourist_happy.png" name="happy" />
            <image src="assets/images/tourist_shocked.png" name="shocked" />
            <image src="assets/images/tourist_sunglasses.png" name="sunglasses" />
        </imagepack>
        
        <imagepack name="background">
            <image src="assets/images/sky.jpg" name="sky" />
        </imagepack>
        
        <character name="f" textbox="tb_main">
            <displayname>Fisher</displayname>
        </character>
        
        <character name="t" textbox="tb_main">
            <displayname>Tourist</displayname>
        </character>
        
        <character name="n" textbox="tb_main"></character>
        
        <textbox name="tb_main" width="890px" height="100px" x="5px" y="355px" namebox="yes" speed="50">
            <nameTemplate>{name}</nameTemplate>
        </textbox>
        
    </assets>
    <scenes>
        
        <scene id="start">
            
            <set asset="background" image="sky" />
            <show asset="background" />
            
            <show asset="tb_main" />
            
            <line s="n">
                Such a nice day...
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                The sun seemed to be smiling as it's rays gently warmed my body.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                Lying on my back on the peer, I was looking up at
                a beautiful sky.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                The sounds of seagulls. Waves crashing against my trusty old boat.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                I caught a lot of fish today. Enough for maybe two days.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                Having done all the work for the day, I could just relax the rest of it.
                Could life be any more fulfilling than that?
            </line>
            
            <hide asset="background" />
            
            <line s="n">
                I took a deep breath and closed my eyes.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                *Click!*
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                Huh?
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                *Click!* *Click!*
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                What the... what is this sound?
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                *Click!*
            </line>
            
            <show asset="background" />
            
            <line s="n">
                Annoyed I opened my eyes.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                It seemed one of those damn rich tourists was taking photographs of god knows what.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                Stuff that obviously only tourists would be interested in. Stones lying around and crap
                like that.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                Although he wore typical tourist clothes, I'd bet my ass that he was some kind of businessman
                in his day-to-day life.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                I could totally imagine him wearing an expensive black suit and one of those
                slave leashes around his neck, which city people seem to be so fond of.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                After taking a photo of my boat, he finally noticed me and waved.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                I turned my head and ignored him. He didn't get the message, obviously, as he approached me further.
            </line>
            
            <set asset="tourist" image="sunglasses" duration="0" />
            <show asset="tourist" />
            
            <line s="t">
                Hello there! I didn't notice you at all before. Did I wake you? Well, sorry about that,
                hahaha!
            </line>
            
            <set asset="tourist" image="happy" />
            
            <line s="n">
                He took off his sunglasses. I could tell that he was much younger than me. 15, maybe 20 years.
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                So.. what are you doing here in the middle of the day?
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Not working? Why not? Are you sick?
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                That annoying little pest just didn't stop bugging me. So I thought it would
                be a good idea to...
            </line>
            
            <choice>
                <option label="... get angry at him." scene="angry"></option>
                <option label="... answer him." scene="answer"></option>
            </choice>
        </scene>
        
        <scene id="angry">
            
            <set asset="tourist" image="shocked" duration="200" />
            
            <line s="f">
                Can you please SHUT UP and leave me the f*** alone? What the heck do you think I'm doing here, huh?
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Well, I...
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                Can't you see I'm trying to sleep here? Do you have eyes in that head of yours?
            </line>
            
            <set asset="tourist" image="calm" duration="200" />
            
            <line s="f">
                Really now, can't you goddamn tourists not just go fall off a cliff or something? 
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                I.. I'm so sorry...
            </line>
            
            <hide asset="tourist" />
            
            <line s="f">
                He left in a hurry. Well, good for him. God knows what I'd do to someone as annoying as him.
            </line>
            
            <restart />
        </scene>
        
        <scene id="answer">
            
            <line s="f">
                ...no.
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Pardon? I didn't quite catch that?
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                No. I'm alright.
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Ah, I see... so why don't you go fishing then? I mean, it's such a nice wheather.
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Aren't these perfect conditions for catching some more fish?
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                I mean... don't you want to take that opportunity?
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Just think about it for a moment. If you would go fishing not once but... say twice. No, maybe even three
                times a day?
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                In no time, you'd be able to get a motor for that boat of yours.
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                And then... let's say a year from now, you could just buy a better boat. You'd be able
                to catch so much more fish like that.
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Oh, I know! Then you could start your own fishing company. You'd hire some men,
                buy some more boats...
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                And before you could even blink you'd be the big boss.
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                You'd be so rich then...
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                And then? What?
            </line>
            
            <line s="t">
                Well, you'd be a made man. You could laze around the coast all day. What a life that'd be, huh?
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                Well, I hate to bring the shocking news to you, but you know... I'm already doing that right now.
            </line>
            
            <set asset="tourist" image="calm" />
            
            <line s="t">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <line s="f">
                ...
            </line>
            
            <hide asset="tourist" />
            
            <line s="n">
                That rendered him speechless. He looked like I told him that his way of life was pointless.
                A total and utter failure. Like he was some dumb idiot and no one ever told him what life was all
                about.
            </line>
            
            <line s="n">
                And maybe... I really did that.
            </line>
            
            <restart />
        </scene>
            
    </scenes>
</ws>